One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I can feel somebody waiting just out of sight, I'll see you soon
Mira amor, ahí estás enfrente mío, esperándome.
Slow your pace, this journey's not done, it's only begun
En nuestra larga travesía que acaba de comenzar, valor, amor, amistad y...
Bravery, friendship, and a bunch of love
And don't forget a little bit of playfulness
...ganas de divertirse, son las cosas que seguiremos teniendo.
We'll treasure those feelings till we're gone
When we’re separated, something doesn’t feel right
(Separated…)
Porque todos somos distintas piezas del mundo,
Like a puzzle missing pieces thrown off to the side
(We’re missing pieces…)
que se unen como compañeros una tras otra.
But just you wait, one day that puzzle will be whole
Mientras las piezas toman forma, el viento seguirá soplando. ¡Sí!
And when we come together, I can feel the wind blowing strong, YEAH!
Feel the wind, take it all in, you’ve gotta let the wind flow by
Así que cuando sientas el viento, debes sentirlo soplar.
Should you feel your eyes welling up, you’ve gotta search out the wind, let it dry your tears
Salgamos a buscar el viento que seque nuestras lágrimas.
On a quest looking for friends, can’t wait to see how big our family gets
Estamos en una aventura para encontrar a ese alguien.
Nothing can stop this dream of mine
I can feel somebody waiting just out of sight, I’ll see you soon
No pararemos. Mira amor, ahí estás enfrente mío, esperándome.
ISLA PENUMBRA
RUINAS DEL REINO DE LA HUMEDAD
ISLA NAMAKURA - TIERRA DE LA POBREZA
HARAHETTERNIA
MAR DEL SUR
REINO DE TORINO
GRAN RUTA MARÍTIMA
ISLA COLOR DE ROSA, REINO TRAVESTI
WEATHERIA
ISLA MECÁNICA
PAÍS DEL FUTURO, BALDIMORE
CIRUGÍA EN
PROGRESO
MAR DEL ESTE
TEQUILA WOLF
GRAN RUTA MARÍTIMA
ARCHIPIELAGO BOYN